https://www.scottdeming.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAboutScott’s BioEvent Prep MaterialServicesKeynoteCustomer Service SpeakerLeadership SpeakerVirtual Keynote SpeakerSeminarsTrainingVirtual TrainingConsultingMultimediaVideosPodcastsClientsShopBlogContact
HomeAboutScott’s BioEvent Prep MaterialServicesKeynoteCustomer Service SpeakerLeadership SpeakerVirtual Keynote SpeakerSeminarsTrainingVirtual TrainingConsultingMultimediaVideosPodcastsClientsShopBlogContact
Your privacy is important to Scott Deming. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that this website collects, and the ways in which that personal information is used.Personal Information Collection Scott Deming may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:information about your use of this website (simple aggregate tracking statistics)information about transactions carried out over this website (including purchases)information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including update emails)any other information that you send to Scott DemingUsing Personal Information Scott Deming may use your personal information to:send to you products that you purchasesupply to you services that you purchasesend you statements and invoicessend you marketing communicationsWhere Scott Deming discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Scott Deming may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.Securing Your Data Scott Deming will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.Updating This Statement Scott Deming may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.Contact Scott Deming If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Scott Deming’s treatment of your personal information, please write to: sdeming@scottdeming.comThis Privacy Statement This privacy statement is based on a precedent created by employmentlawcontracts.co.uk and published by freenetlaw.com.ContactScott Deming 7313 Ivy Hill Lane Waxhaw, NC 28173704-256-5256 info@scottdeming.com Newsletter SignupEmail* By providing your email address you are agreeing to receive newsletters and information from Scott Deming. We will not share your information with anyone.CAPTCHA
Stay Connected Copyright All Rights Reserved © 2018 HomeEvent Prep MaterialContactPrivacy PolicyData Collection Privacy PolicyTerms of UseSitemap
